papermag.com 2012-06-24

# PAPERMAG - Privacy Policy

**PRIVACY POLICY**  
Thank you for visiting the Paper Magazine site.  Your privacy is important to us.  To better protect your privacy, we would like you to know how we use the information you provide to us.  This notice explains what personal information is collected, how this information is used, and with whom we share such information.  Please take a few minutes to read our privacy policy so that you understand our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

 **Information Collected**  
We collect personally identifiable information (such as your name, address, e-mail address and credit card information) when you subscribe to our magazine, register for our monthly and VIP emails and newsletters, or register for any portion of our services.  Optional information such as your age, gender, interests and hobbies may also be requested.

We also collect non-personally identifiable information (such as your IP address or domain, or about your site usage) for purposes of site administration or improvement, and to compile aggregate information about usage of this site.

 **Use of Information**  
Paper Magazine collects personal information in order to provide guests with a personalized online experience and to provide our advertisers with a way to reach the right audience.  We may use the information you provide to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about offerings, and to offer you other products, programs, services, companies or events that we believe may be of interest to you.  We may also use the information to communicate with you, such as send you our newsletter, notify you about events or promotions, contact you about your subscription, or to improve the services that we offer by tailoring them to your needs.

On a confidential basis, Paper Magazine may also share personal information with our corporate affiliates or consultants or with third parties that perform a particular service on our behalf (such as keeping track of subscriptions, marketing, printing, mailing, credit card processing, or general site administration), and may also share aggregate information with third parties for advertising and promotional purposes.  We may also disclose personal information in response to a legal process, such as a request by law enforcement, a court order or subpoena, or to protect the integrity of our site if we believe that a guest has committed unlawful or otherwise harmful acts.

 **Use of Cookies**  
Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes.  Cookies make Web-surfing easier by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you are at a site.  Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliated companies.  Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well.  We do not have any control over cookies placed by advertisers.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our site.  For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our Web page (i.e. to recognize you by name when you return to our site), or to save your password in password-protected areas.  We may also use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.  While your personally identifiable information is protected as outlined above, we may use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

If you don't want cookies, your Web browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them.  However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of this site may not function properly if you do so.

Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at our Web site.  Once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

   **Use of IP Address**  
An IP address (Internet Protocol address) is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you log on to the Web.  Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address, so when a guest requests pages from our site, our servers log the guest's IP address.  The IP addresses of our guests are collected only for the purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers, our corporate affiliates or consultants, or with third parties that perform a particular service on our behalf.  We do not combine IP addresses with any personally identifiable information, nor do we compile any session activity reports by IP address.

   **Third-Party Use**  
When registering for a subscription or to receive our monthly or VIP emails or newsletters on this site, Paper Magazine provides visitors with an opportunity to receive offers from advertisers and other companies who have services, products, and offers that we think might be of interest to you.  If you do not at that time indicate a preference not to receive such offers, Paper Magazine will from time to time provide your contact information to these entities so that they may send you these offers.  If you do not decline to receive such offers at the time you provide your information or if you change your mind and no longer want us to share your contact information with others, send an e-mail to [vip@papermag.com](mailto:vip@papermag.com) as described in the Privacy Options section below.

If you provide information to Paper Magazine in connection with a promotion with a third-party entity or web site linked to this site (such as the purchase of other products), the information you provide will be used for the purpose for which you provided the information and will be shared with that third-party entity.  These third-party entities may obtain personally identifiable information that guests voluntarily submit to participate in the promotion.  Paper Magazine has no control over the third-party entities' use of this information.  Your personal information may also be used for other purposes that may be disclosed at the time your information is requested.

 **Security**  
Paper Magazine has implemented appropriate safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and to make proper use of the information we collect.  However, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure.  Thus, while we strive to protect your personal information, Paper Magazine cannot absolutely guarantee the security of the any information you provide to us. 

Agents and contractors of Paper Magazine who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Paper Magazine.

 In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your personally identifiable information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development.  If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your e-mail address, we may notify you by e-mail.  By using this Web site, you consent to our use of e-mail as a means of such notification.

Any unauthorized access to or use of the Paper Magazine Web site or information collected and maintained by Paper Magazine Web site should be immediately brought to the attention of Paper Magazine at the customer service e-mail address below.  Paper Magazine will investigate, and if necessary take action to prevent or halt, any violation of this Privacy Policy of which it becomes aware.

  **Privacy Options**  
You have the right to "opt-out" of certain Paper Magazine uses of your personal information.  At the time you are requested to provide personal information on this site, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to, receive e-mail offers from Paper Magazine or have your personal information shared with other companies.  You may also make this request by sending an e-mail to [vip@papermag.com](mailto:vip@papermag.com).  In this e-mail please say whether you would like to opt-out of receiving e-mail offers from Paper Magazine and/or having your personal information shared with other companies.  Please understand that if you opt-out of receiving e-mails from Paper Magazine, we may still contact you by e-mail in connection with your account with us or to provide you with important information about Paper Magazine or this site.  Also, a request to have us stop sharing your personal information with other companies will only apply as of the date of the request, and Paper Magazine will not be responsible for any communications that you may receive from companies that received your personal information prior to your request.  In these cases, please contact that company directly.

If you prefer not to receive traditional mail or other off-line promotions from Paper Magazine, please send us an e-mail at <a href="mailto:vip@papermag.com">vip@papermag.com</a>.  Paper Magazine will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt-out of these unrelated uses.

 **Note to Parents**  
Children should always ask permission before providing any personal information online.  No information should be submitted to or posted on this site by any Minor (a guest under 18 years of age) without the consent of a parent or guardian.  Unless otherwise disclosed during collection, we do not knowingly provide any personally identifiable information about minors, regardless of its source, to third parties, nor is this information knowingly used by Paper Magazine for any marketing or promotional purposes.

        **Policy Modification**  
This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time, without notice to users of this site.  Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to the Web site.

 **How to Access or Correct Information**  
For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that this Paper Magazine site has collected about you, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please email us at [vip@papermag.com](mailto:vip@papermag.com).  
To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

 **How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions or concerns about any aspect of this Privacy Policy or its implementation please contact us via e-mail at [vip@papermag.com](mailto:vip@papermag.com) or at the following address:

PAPER Magazine  
Privacy Policy Coordinator/Customer Service  
15 E. 32nd St. 11th Fl.  
New York, NY 10016
